followone.com 2016-11-30

# Followone - Privacy Policy

Thank you for using this site! We wrote this policy to help you understand what information we collect, how we use it, and what choices you have. Because we’re an internet company, some of the concepts below are a little technical, but we’ve tried our best to explain things in a simple and clear way. We welcome your questions and comments on this policy. 

We collect information in two ways: 

**1\. When you give it to us or give us permission to obtain it.**

When you sign up for or use our products, you voluntarily give us certain information. This can include your name, profile photo, comments, likes, email address you used to sign up, and any other information you provide us. If you’re using this site on your mobile device, you can also choose to provide us with location data. You also may give us permission to access your information in other services. For example, you may link your Facebook or Twitter account, which allows us to obtain information from those accounts (e.g., your friends or contacts). The information we obtain from those services often depends on your settings or their privacy policies, so be sure to check what those are. 

**2\. We also get technical information when you use our products or use websites or apps that have features from this site.**

These days, whenever you use a website, mobile application, or other Internet service, there’s certain information that almost always gets created and recorded automatically. The same is true when you use our products. Here are some of the types of information we collect: 

**a.** Log Data. When you use this site or go to a webpage or use an app that has features (like our “Share” button), our servers automatically record information (“log data”) including information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website or your mobile app sends when you’re using it. This log data may include your Internet Protocol address, the address of the web pages you visited that had features from this site, browser type and settings, the date and time of your request, how you used this website, and cookie data. 

**b.** Cookie data. Depending on how you’re accessing our products, we may use “cookies” (a small text file sent by your computer each time you visit our website, unique to your account or your browser), or similar technologies to record log data. When we use cookies, we may use “session” cookies (that last until you close your browser) or “persistent” cookies (that last until you or your browser delete them). For example, we may use cookies to store your language preferences or other settings so you don‘t have to set them up every time you visit this site. Some of the cookies we use are associated with your account (including personal information about you, such as the email address you gave us), and other cookies are not. 

**c.** Device Information. In addition to log data, we may also collect information about the device you’re using this site on, including what type of device it is, what operating system you’re using, device settings, unique device identifiers, and crash data. Whether we collect some or all of this information often depends on what type of device you’re using and its settings. For example, different types of information are available depending on whether you’re using a Mac or a PC, or an iPhone or an Android phone. To learn more about what information your device makes available to us, please also check the policies of your device manufacturer or software provider. 

We use the information we collect to provide our products to you and make them better, develop new products, and protect our users. For example, we may log how often people use two different versions of a product, which can help us understand which version is better. 

We also use the information we collect to offer you customized content, including: 

**a.** Suggesting content you might like. For example, if you’ve indicated that you’re interested in cooking or visited recipe websites that has features from this site, we may suggest food-related content, or people that we think you might like; 

**b.** Showing you ads you might be interested in. 

We also use the information we collect to: 

**a.** Send you updates (such as when certain activity, like shares or comments), newsletters, marketing materials and other information that may be of interest to you. For example, depending on your email notification settings, we may send you weekly updates that include posts you may like. You can decide to stop getting these updates by updating your account settings (or through other settings we may provide). 

**b.** Help your friends and contacts find you on this site. For example, if you sign up using a Facebook account, we may help your Facebook friends find your account on this site when they first sign up. Or, we may allow people to search for your account using your email address. 

**c.** Respond to your questions or comments. 

The information we collect may be “personally identifiable” (meaning it can be used to specifically identify you as a unique person) or “non-personally identifiable” (meaning it can’t be used to specifically identify you). 

People use this website to find their inspirations, make them a reality, and inspire others in the process. When you post public updates, anyone can view them. You may also provide us with profile page information that anyone can view. The other limited instances where we may share your personal information include: 

**a.** When we have your consent. This includes sharing information with other services (like Facebook or Twitter) when you’ve chosen to link to your account to those services or publish your activity to them. For example, you can choose to publish your posts to Facebook or Twitter. 

**b.** If we believe that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety, rights, or property of the public, any person; or to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues. 

**c.** We may engage in a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganization, or similar transaction or proceeding that involves the transfer of the information described in this Policy. 

We may also share aggregated or non-personally identifiable information with our partners or others. 

We are not directed to children under 13. If you learn that your minor child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us. 

We may change this policy from time to time, and if we do we’ll post any changes on this page. If you continue to use this website after those changes are in effect, you agree to the revised policy. If the changes are significant, we may provide more prominent notice or obtain your consent as required by law.
